<resources>
    <string name="app_name">30 Days Of Wellness</string>
    <string name="day_1_title">Mindful Breathing</string>
    <string name="day_1_description">Start your journey by focusing on your breath. Spend 10 minutes practicing mindful breathing to center yourself and reduce stress.</string>
    <string name="day_2_title">Hydration Boost</string>
    <string name="day_2_description">Increase your water intake today. Aim for at least 8 glasses of water to keep your body hydrated and functioning optimally.</string>
    <string name="day_3_title">Morning Stretch</string>
    <string name="day_3_description">Begin your day with a 15-minute stretching routine to improve flexibility and wake up your muscles.</string>
    <string name="day_4_title">Nature Walk</string>
    <string name="day_4_description">Take a walk in nature. Spend at least 30 minutes outdoors to refresh your mind and body.</string>
    <string name="day_5_title">Healthy Eating</string>
    <string name="day_5_description">Incorporate more fruits and vegetables into your meals today. Aim for a colorful plate to ensure a variety of nutrients.</string>
    <string name="day_6_title">Digital Detox</string>
    <string name="day_6_description">Unplug from all electronic devices for at least two hours. Use this time to engage in offline activities you enjoy.</string>
    <string name="day_7_title">Gratitude Journal</string>
    <string name="day_7_description">Write down three things you are grateful for. Reflecting on positive aspects of your life can improve your mood and outlook.</string>
    <string name="day_8_title">Strength Training</string>
    <string name="day_8_description">Incorporate a 20-minute strength training workout to build muscle and boost your metabolism.</string>
    <string name="day_9_title">Deep Sleep</string>
    <string name="day_9_description">Prioritize a good nights sleep by creating a relaxing bedtime routine. Aim for 7-9 hours of uninterrupted sleep.</string>
    <string name="day_10_title">Meditation</string>
    <string name="day_10_description">Spend 10-15 minutes meditating to calm your mind and reduce anxiety.</string>
    <string name="day_11_title">Balanced Meals</string>
    <string name="day_11_description">Plan and prepare balanced meals for the day, focusing on incorporating proteins, carbohydrates, and healthy fats.</string>
    <string name="day_12_title">Social Connection</string>
    <string name="day_12_description">Reach out to a friend or family member. Social interactions can boost your mental well-being.</string>
    <string name="day_13_title">Creative Expression</string>
    <string name="day_13_description">Engage in a creative activity such as drawing, painting, writing, or playing music to stimulate your mind and reduce stress.</string>
    <string name="day_14_title">Cardio Workout</string>
    <string name="day_14_description">Do a 30-minute cardio workout to increase your heart rate and improve cardiovascular health.</string>
    <string name="day_15_title">Mindful Eating</string>
    <string name="day_15_description">Practice mindful eating by paying attention to your food, savoring each bite, and eating without distractions.</string>
    <string name="day_16_title">Positive Affirmations</string>
    <string name="day_16_description">Start your day with positive affirmations to set a positive tone and boost your self-esteem.</string>
    <string name="day_17_title">Yoga Session</string>
    <string name="day_17_description">Try a 20-minute yoga session to improve flexibility, strength, and mental clarity.</string>
    <string name="day_18_title">Self-Care Routine</string>
    <string name="day_18_description">Dedicate time to a self-care activity you enjoy, such as taking a bath, reading a book, or enjoying a hobby.</string>
    <string name="day_19_title">Volunteer</string>
    <string name="day_19_description">Spend time volunteering or helping someone in need. Giving back can enhance your sense of purpose and happiness.</string>
    <string name="day_20_title">Mindfulness Walk</string>
    <string name="day_20_description">Take a walk, paying attention to your surroundings. Notice the sights, sounds, and smells to ground yourself in the present moment.</string>
    <string name="day_21_title">Meal Prep</string>
    <string name="day_21_description">Prepare healthy meals for the week ahead to ensure you have nutritious options readily available.</string>
    <string name="day_22_title">Financial Wellness</string>
    <string name="day_22_description">Review your financial situation and create a budget or savings plan to reduce stress related to money.</string>
    <string name="day_23_title">Hobby Time</string>
    <string name="day_23_description">Spend at least 30 minutes on a hobby or activity that brings you joy and relaxation.</string>
    <string name="day_24_title">Relaxation Techniques</string>
    <string name="day_24_description">Practice relaxation techniques such as progressive muscle relaxation, deep breathing, or guided imagery.</string>
    <string name="day_25_title">Outdoor Exercise</string>
    <string name="day_25_description">Combine the benefits of nature and exercise by engaging in an outdoor workout, such as jogging, cycling, or hiking.</string>
    <string name="day_26_title">Unplug Before Bed</string>
    <string name="day_26_description">Turn off all screens at least an hour before bed to improve your sleep quality.</string>
    <string name="day_27_title">Learn Something New</string>
    <string name="day_27_description">Challenge your brain by learning a new skill or hobby. This could be anything from cooking a new recipe to learning a new language.</string>
    <string name="day_28_title">Express Gratitude</string>
    <string name="day_28_description">Write a letter of gratitude to someone who has made a positive impact on your life.</string>
    <string name="day_29_title">Body Scan Meditation</string>
    <string name="day_29_description">Practice a body scan meditation to become aware of physical sensations and release tension.</string>
    <string name="day_30_title">Reflect and Plan</string>
    <string name="day_30_description">Reflect on the past 30 days and identify any positive changes or habits you have developed. Plan how to continue incorporating wellness into your daily life.</string>
</resources>
